https://ncpta.org/index.php/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy for the NCPTA Website
The North Carolina Parent Teacher Association is committed to protecting the privacy of its members and has adopted the following policy about the gathering and dissemination of personal information at the NCPTA website, www.ncpta.org
In general, you may visit the NCPTA website without submitting any personal information. However, NCPTA may request member information in order to provide services, resources, and information, including newsletters, networking opportunities, webinars, and event information, to its members.  Member information submitted will be used only for PTA purposes.
Website Administration
The NCPTA web server maintains a standard log file of visitors to the site that automatically records your IP address or that of the service you use to connect to the Internet (such as AOL). No personal information is attached to this address. The NCPTA may use this IP address to help diagnose problems with the server and to administer the website. This address is not shared with any third parties or used for any other purpose.
Other Sites
The NCPTA websites contain links to other websites. The NCPTA is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other websites.
If you have questions or comments about the NCPTA privacy policy, please write to office@ncpta.org.
PTA Member Benefits
NCPTA members are offered special discounts and other unique opportunities.
PTA Mission
To make every child’s potential a reality by engaging and empowering families and communities to advocate for all children.
